Welcome to our AI tutorial series. Today we'll be learning about machine learning fundamentals.
Machine learning is a subset of artificial intelligence that allows computers to learn automatically.
There are three main types of machine learning: supervised, unsupervised, and reinforcement learning.
Supervised learning uses labeled data to train models. For example, showing a computer thousands of cat photos.
Unsupervised learning finds patterns in data without labels. It's like finding hidden connections.
Reinforcement learning learns through trial and error, much like how humans learn to play games.
Popular machine learning algorithms include linear regression, decision trees, and neural networks.
Neural networks are inspired by the human brain and can solve complex problems.
Deep learning is a subset of machine learning that uses multi-layered neural networks.
Applications of machine learning include image recognition, natural language processing, and recommendation systems.
To get started with machine learning, you need data, a problem to solve, and the right tools.
Popular tools include Python, TensorFlow, PyTorch, and scikit-learn.
The future of machine learning includes automated machine learning and explainable AI.
Thank you for watching this introduction to machine learning. Subscribe for more AI content!